I suppose we could just wait here until
we're inevitably overwhelmed by our
attackers or I might suggest that
someone begin breaching the door breach
initiated now we wait
patience is not my strong suit I suspect
we'll find something to occupy your time
start in the breach might take a while I
see that everything is running as
smoothly as ever
things go more smoothly when we act like
professionals
a pity we'll miss the masquerade I have
the perfect costume didn't think that
would be your scene there's a lot of
things you don't know about me you're
not the only one who likes to dress up
breaching process is still underway
we're making progress on the door how's
everyone doing uh-huh
couldn't be better just grande here
Talon seems very committed to ending our
lives better to kill them now than wait
for another surprise attack ironic
that was certainly a decisive solution
to the Antoniou problem it's not how we
do things well it seems we've had a
change in methodology a little too much
change
no sign of rescue does nothing run on
time here how are you feeling commander
fine no ill-effects so far let me know
if that changes
so much for keeping a low profile the
entire city must be awake now and here I
thought we were supposed to be the quiet
ones let's just get out of here alive
perhaps next time we might select a less
suicidal plan of attack I wouldn't
describe this as light resistance
quality intelligence we've received it
makes no difference to me how droll
you did would need it to be done Gabriel
don't apologize
I never have and I don't intend to start
now
and getting shot at and getting shot at
you two are adorable
fancy place here try to leave everything
in one piece well tell that to them you
call this art a child could have made it
I never took you for an art critic never
had the eye for it anyway
Philistines
you could all do with a little culture
the cowboy especially I'm plenty
cultured
have you ever been to the cave of
mystery didn't think so
I'm the only one who feels hungry that
could be an unforeseen side effect I was
making a joke you sound disappointed I
heard it was a good time
McCree we need to talk about your
Italian accent I watched a bunch of Old
Spaghetti Westerns I thought it was
pretty good
buona sera signora can I get you
something to drink please never do that
again
Antonia was right about one thing you
will take the blame for this always have
I don't need the statues and medals
anyway what's keeping our ride we can't
wait forever something tells me the army
of bad guys converging in our position
isn't helping macri's instincts are as
ever unimpeachable I really anticipate
the debriefing on this debacle we need
to stay alive until we can be evacuated
next thing you know we'll have
lieutenant Wilhelm on the team I take it
all in my stride no way out from here
unbelievable
past time for us to depart I'm sure we
could find a way to repair the damage